Guide to the Harry H. Weintraub Collection of Gay-Related Photography and Historical Documentation, 1850s-2010.
Weintraub, Harry H. Collection of Gay-Related Photography and Historical Documentation
- Photographs
  - Young, Dr.
    - Medium format, Items (Box B158)
    - Medium format, Items (Box B159)
  - Young, Dr./Thermalaids/Condom Molds
    - Medium format, Items (Box B96)
- Additional images, CD-2364
- Posters and Oversized Images
  - Tony Sansone Poster (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Pop-up Poster (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Broadway Production of "Bent" Photo - Richard Gere and David Dukes, 1980 (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Nickerson Lumber Co Boy Scouts of America Poster (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - DSI Poster 8 (Mapcase-folder 2)
  - Oversized Drawings (Mapcase-folder 2)
  - Colt Studios Ship Shape (Mapcase-folder 2)
  - Marlon Brando Posters (Mapcase-folder 2)
  - Navy Posters (Mapcase-folder 2)
  - Wall House 2 - John Hedjuk - Cooper Union Exhibit Poster, November 6-30, 2001 (Mapcase-folder 3)
  - Photoflexion - Art Zeller, Franco Columbu, Signed Exhibit Poster (Mapcase-folder 3)
  - Forbidden Love - Movie Poster (Mapcase-folder 3)
  - Day Without Art: International Day of Action and Mourning in Response to the AIDS Crisis, December 1, 1989 (Mapcase-folder 3)
  - Helvey Stalked Schindler into a Public Toilet and Beat Him [To Death] Because He was a Homosexual - Poster, 1993 (Mapcase-folder 3)
  - To Die For: Radioman Allen R. Schindler: 1971-1992 - Poster (Mapcase-folder 3)
  - "The Eminent Yiddish Artist Bernard Elving" Framed Print (Mapcase-item 1)
  - Sizi Lianische Bavernehre - Pietro Mascagni, Caralleria Rusticana Framed Print (Mapcase-item 2)
- CD's
  - Various color/black and white physique photos by Mark Lynch, 2003-2007; CD-3471-3500 (Box A112)